Shatty Bull Cat Silly Queen Determination Tournament
634 points
Correct!!!
Excellent!
Correct!
I'm done!
You walk like an idiot!
Twenty-three percent.
Let's keep up the good work, ladies and gentlemen.
What is the name of this microbe over here?
Oh, oh, oh, oh!
Come on, which one is it?
Blinky Eye.
Gentle.
Come on, Mr. Smooth, let's go.
Daphnia
Correct answer
Cute
Cute.
I got your hair.
Let's go.
How much is 70 percent off 2,000 yen?
What?
I don't know.
Please tell me.
I'm sorry.Too bad.
What?
Oh, yeah.
Huh?
Ha-ha-ha-ha!
Okay.
Ready, go!
Ah! Here it comes! Let's go, Mr. Matsumoto!
You want to add 70% of 2,000 yen?
Yes, 600 yen! Correct!
Whoo-hoo!
Are you done? What? Are you done?
Yes! It's over! Oh, my God!
Wow! That's great!
I thought you were a smart group! Really!
No! No, they look stupid with Westerners! I knew it!
Really!
They are a great group! Heh!
Now, the biggest problem is that the leader is still here!
I want to quit!
Let's go! What do you think of button meat?
What? Button meat?
Well, it's kind of a trick, but..,
But this group doesn't need any trickery.
What do you know?
Button meat is wild boar meat?
What kind of meat is Sakura meat?
Cherry blossoms? You've heard of sakura, right?
Sakura?
Sakura? Cherry blossoms?
Cherry blossoms?
Cherry blossoms? Whale?
Cherry blossoms? Whale? Whale?
Cherry blossom whale?
Cherry blossom pezilla?
Underground, underground, underground, underground.
Um, it's not a one-sentence multiple-answer question.
Please step back.
Please back off.
Here's your chance.
Because a button is a wild boar, which means you can eat it, right?
That means you can probably eat them.
Can't you eat it?
Hmm? You can eat them.
Can't you eat them?
You can eat it.
Yes, yes, yes.
Ah, here he comes.
Mr. Omiyama.
Bird.
Too bad.
The bird is chicken meat.
Indeed.
It's a pity.
That's right. I've never heard of it.
But if you do, you might hit it.
It's just something,It's kind of,
Does it change the way you eat?
That's right.
Let's say you've eaten meat before.
Yes, I have.
Here it comes. Hina-san.
Rabbit. What a pity!
Some places eat rabbit. I've never had it, but it looks like Sakura.
Amazing!
Hina-san, please push it in a little.
It's like chara-men.
If you go there already, you might hit it.
Kitsuji?
No, sir!
Pheasant is a word for lamb and mutton.
So, you want to go either way?
That's good. Let's go.
What is it?
Hmm.
Mmm-hmm.
Sing a song.
Yes.
It's the meat of number 3, isn't it?
Anything. Anything.
Shucks!
What a shame!
What?
Can anyone recognize it?
Yes, I do.Yes, I understand.
I understand quite well.
Are you Etsukay?
I love it. Uma.
Correct!
Yay!
Good job!
The best!
It's a horse, sir. Now, one of us can get out of here.
Let's go. What do you call a perfect game of bowling?
Perfect game.
It's so good. It's so good.
What's that, just for saying it?
You've played bowling before, right?
Strike?
What? Out! Out! Out! Out!
Natsumi is out.
Okay? What's the score?
What's a strike?
Ten, ten, ten, ten, ten, ten, ten.
What?
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight, nine, ten, ten, ten.
Ha-ha-ha-ha-ha.
Huh?
100!
No way! One more time!
I'll put it away.
What? What?
No way.
That's what I thought.
I felt like a hundred.
I thought you'd say 100.
One thousand!
Ha-ha-ha-ha!
So this is how you calculate.
Now, that means if you say the score, there's a chance it will match!
Come on, chance, let's go
Here we go.
Eight hundred and fifty points.
Too bad.
Twic.
That's a little higher than Twick's.
Too bad.
Two more to go.
Let's do the math, everyone.
I'm doing the math.
I think we can do it.
Let's do it.
Seventy.
Too bad.
Too bad. Yes, too bad.
Yes, I'm sorry.
Last one.
Hey, guys, Mr. Mogiyama.
Pants?
12001200
What a surprise!
I wonder if everyone is laughing at the 1,000 point stage.
I don't know.
Oh, wait, is that it?
You go bowling and throw like an idiot?
Don't even think about it.
I throw like an idiot all the time, thinking, "If I get a score like this, this is what happens.
It's so frustrating!
Throw while thinking.
That's good.
I can't wait to see you throw.
Thank you.
Here we go.
If you drive for two hours at 60 kilometers an hour, how many kilometers will you go?
Next. Next.
No, no, no, wait a minute. It's easy.
How many kilometers would you go if you drove for two hours at 60 kilometers per hour?
If you run for 2 hours at 60 km/h, how many kilometers will you go?
If you run for 2 hours
120 kilometers.
Correct.
Yes!
Yay!
Now, the makeup is ready. Thank you.
That was good.
The group has decided on the idiots.
But let's decide on number one. Let's go.But let's decide on number one. Here we go.
Please answer the formula for finding the area of a triangle.
Yes.
Base x Height / 2
Correct!
Wrong, wrong. Mr. Matsumoto, you look like you're doing great, but you're terrible.
What about my face?
Let's go into details.
What is the base ice cream made of?
I don't know.
I don't know, but it's okay. I don't know, but let's go with it.
Ice?
I don't know.
I don't know. Ice is solidified by water.
Don't you know that?
That's good.
Here you go.
You got it?
All right.
Carbon dioxide.
Correct!
Excellent. Now, we're at the top of the summit line.
Okay, I got it.
Here we go. It's going to be a fool's decision.
I know I said it's going to be a fool's decision, but it's already a fool's decision.
I just forgot about it.
Let's go.
What do you think it means?
Matsumoto!
You're early, Matsumoto-san.Mr. Matsumoto was quick.
Oh, this is wrong.
Wait a minute.
I just wondered how to read it.
You don't read it.
Seriously, I didn't.
I'm so embarrassed.
Let's start over.
Let's go. The last question.
The world's first astronaut,
Gagarin, the world's first astronaut.
What was the Earth?
I don't know.
I know, I know, I know.
Let's go, everyone.
The earth was a circle.
Too bad!
The earth is indeed round.
Gagarin's famous words.
What was the earth?
It was blue.
Correct!
I did it.
So, here she is,
The queen of stupidity, Hina Aku-san.
Congratulations!
That was close. That was close.
That was great.
Then go ahead to the tip.
I feel like I'm going to pussy out, a little bit.
I feel like I'm gonna pussy out.
Um, who would you like to share your joy with?
Oh, I want to tell my mom.
I don't think you should tell her.
She'll be sad.
Okay, last but not least,
What would you like to say to your fans on camera?
Please say a few words in four-character idioms.
Please use 4-character idioms.
Yes.
Thank you very much for your support.
Tenku Tenshita?
I am Yoshikubo.
Well, well, it's not a four-character idiom. It's a word that follows.
Certainly, certainly.
You know it, don't you?
Yes, it is a four-character idiom. Tianjing tianjing.
I like it. You ended with full throttle, didn't you?
Thank you very much. Well, that's all for now,
This is the Cathywell Cat Silly Castle.